Yes, I'd be surprised.
はい、びっくりしちゃう
Are you surprised?
びっくりしちゃうの?
I somehow dropped it.
なんか一応落としてきた
what?
なに?
I dropped something.
なんかくちくち落としてきたよ
It's spread out properly, properly.
ちゃんと広げてんだよ、ちゃんと
Spread it out and show it to me properly.
広 げて見せて、ちゃんと
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Wait a minute, don't leave.
ちょっと待って、抜けないで
Remove your shoulders.
肩を抜いて
Pull it out comfortably.
気持ちよく抜いて
It's just the mouth.
口だけだって
child
こ
Just a little leg.
っち の足さ、ちょっと
Can you give it to me?
あげられる?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
like this?
こう?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It looks good.
よく見えるよ
Do you want to turn it on?
つける?
Yeah.
うん
It's just a wish, but please don't put it on.
願いなんだけどさ、 ほんまにつけないで、
Is it okay?
していいかな
Oh, no.
え、だめだよ
Wish.
願い
Um, no.
うーん、だめだよ
Don't you feel?
気持ちくない?
I have to feel it.
気持ちなきゃ
Usually, but just for today.
普段はそうだけど、 今日だけ
please.
お願い
Got it.
分かった
Take it outside.
外に出してね
Outside?
外に?
Take it outside.
外に出す
Promise me, okay.
約束ね、ちゃんと
promise.
約束
It's just the tip.
先っぽだけだよ
Don't you feel?
気持ちくない?
Isn't it wrong?
違うでしょ?
You can see it, right?
見えるでしょ?
I'm throwing up myself
自 分で吐いてるの
kana?
かな?
Should I press it?
押 してばいい?
By yourself.
自分で
It's okay to take it slow.
ゆ っくりでいいよ
Yeah.
うん
It's okay to take it slow.
ゆっくりでいいよ
Sit tight.
よ くついて
slowly.
ゆっくり
Please go over there too.
あっちのほうも行ってごらん
Okay, go at least once.
いいよ、1回も行ってごらん
Throw it up yourself.
自分で吐いて
By yourself.
自分で
Try throwing up yourself.
自分で吐いてごらん
It's artificial.
人工だ
My last wish.
最後の願い
I'll take you to high-class Yakiniku twice,
高級焼肉2回連れて行ってあげるから、
Please forgive me.
許して
I did it.
やった
Did you get it?
もらえたっけ?
Really?
本当に?
I'll give you some medicine too.
お薬も渡すし
Let's take another photo.
また撮影しようね
Understood.
わかった
Thank you.
ありがとうね
bye bye.
バイバイ
Hello.
こんにちは
Thank you for your hard work, Meki-chan.
めきちゃん、お疲れ様
thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様です
Were you taking it easy?
ゆっくりしてた?
A warm bath.
温かいお風呂
Meki-chan, it's not a bit dry, though.
めきちゃんさ、 ちょっと乾燥じゃないけどさ、
I wish I could get something like that.
そういうのもらえたらな
how was it?
どうだった?
it was fun.
楽しかった
it was fun?
楽しかった?
Really?
本当に?
But, seriously, I met an old man,
だけどさ、マジでさ、 出会って おっさんとはね、
About a year or so.
1年ちょっとくらいか
Seriously, the Yakiniku was really good.
マジでさ、 焼肉、本当に手でたけど
Seriously?
マジで?
Seriously.
マジで
I'll take you seriously.
マジで連れて行く
So, well, viewers,
でさ、 まあ さ、 視聴者さん、
As a buyer, I wish I could say something.
購入者さんでさ、 何 か一言あればいいんだけど
amazing.
すごい
You can see the camera, right?
カメラ見えるでしょ、これ
appear.
見える
Somehow,
なんか、
Please enjoy my video.
私 のビデオを 楽しんでください
cute.
かわいい
So cute.
めっちゃかわいい
It was fun.
楽しかったね
it was fun.
楽しかった
thank you.
ありがとう
No, thank you very much.
いや、こちらこそ本当にありがとう
see you later.
じゃあまたね
Bye bye.
バイバーイ